Voices of Civil Rights Project collection
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series III: Bus Tour Interviews and Events Sound Recordings, 2004-2005
  - Subseries I: Sound Recordings, 2004, 219 sound discs (minidiscs), 79 sound cassettes and 10 microcassettes
    - AFC 2005/015: SR226, 1 minidisc
      - Richard Cruce interviewed by Vern Smith in Atlanta, Georgia, 2004-09-24
    - AFC 2005/015: SR227, 1 minidisc
      - Kathryn Hickerson interviewed by Vern Smith in New Albany, Indiana, 2004-10-01
      - James Hickerson interviewed by Vern Smith in New Albany, Indiana, 2004-10-01
    - AFC 2005/015: SR228, 1 minidisc
      - Walter Cates, Sr., interviewed by Vern Smith in Columbus, Ohio, 2004-09-28
    - AFC 2005/015: SR229, 1 minidisc
      - Gary Leavell interviewed by Vern Smith in New Albany, Indiana, 2004-10-01
      - Betty Jo Jumper Holloway interviewed by Vern Smith in New Albany, Indiana, 2004-10-01
    - AFC 2005/015: SR230, 1 minidisc
      - James Brown, Jr., interviewed by Vern Smith in Detroit, Michigan, 2004-09-30
      - Ruth Mathews interviewed by Vern Smith in Detroit, Michigan, 2004-09-30
      - Rennie Lewis-Epps interviewed by Vern Smith in Detroit, Michigan, 2004-09-30
      - Doris Watkins interviewed by Vern Smith in Detroit, Michigan, 2004-09-30
    - AFC 2005/015: SR231, 1 minidisc
      - Daniel Parker interviewed by Vern Smith in Chicago, Illinois, 2004-10-04
      - Pearl Cartman interviewed by Vern Smith in Chicago, Illinois, 2004-10-04
      - Barbara Frederick interviewed by Vern Smith in Chicago, Illinois, 2004-10-04
      - Ernestine Ridgnal interviewed by Vern Smith in Chicago, Illinois, 2004-10-04
    - AFC 2005/015: SR232, 1 minidisc
      - Zella Harrington interviewed by Vern Smith in St. Louis, Missouri, 2004-10-06
    - AFC 2005/015: SR233, 1 minidisc
      - Ada Shine Hollingsworth interviewed by Vern Smith in Little Rock, Arkansas, 2004-09-25
      - Diane Curry interviewed by Vern Smith in Little Rock, Arkansas, 2004-09-25
    - AFC 2005/015: SR234, 1 minidisc
      - Wade Henderson interviewed by Nery Ynclan in Washington, D.C., 2004-08-03
    - AFC 2005/015: SR235, 1 minidisc
      - Elias Garcia interviewed by Sandra Marquez in Topeka, Kansas, 2004-08-04
      - Dennis Vasquez interviewed by Sandra Marquez in Topeka, Kansas, 2004-08-04
    - AFC 2005/015: SR236, 1 minidisc
      - Gloria Shields interviewed by Sandra Marquez in Jackson, Mississippi, 2004-08-22
      - Celestine King interviewed by Sandra Marquez in Jackson, Mississippi, 2004-08-22
      - Ada Robinson interviewed by Sandra Marquez in Jackson, Mississippi, 2004-08-22
      - Lottie Thornton interviewed by Sandra Marquez in Jackson, Mississippi, 2004-08-22
      - Exie Williamson interviewed by Sandra Marquez in Jackson, Mississippi, 2004-08-22
      - Viola Toney interviewed by Sandra Marquez in Jackson, Mississippi, 2004-08-22
    - AFC 2005/015: SR237, 1 minidisc
      - Carlene Davis interviewed by Sandra Marquez in St. Louis, Missouri, 2004-10-06
      - David Nelson interviewed by Sandra Marquez in St. Louis, Missouri, 2004-10-06
    - AFC 2005/015: SR238, 1 minidisc
      - Della Goodwin interviewed by Sandra Marquez in Detroit, Michigan, 2004-09-30
      - Ernestine Cox interviewed by Sandra Marquez in Detroit, Michigan, 2004-09-30
      - Alma Greer interviewed by Sandra Marquez in Detroit, Michigan, 2004-09-30
      - Patricia Stokes interviewed by Sandra Marquez in Detroit, Michigan, 2004-09-30
    - AFC 2005/015: SR239, 1 minidisc
      - Shirley Sharpley interviewed by Sandra Marquez in Detroit, Michigan, 2004-09-30
    - AFC 2005/015: SR240, 1 minidisc
      - Merle Harl interviewed by Sandra Marquez in New Albany, Indiana, 2004-10-01
      - Kenneth Scrivner interviewed by Sandra Marquez in New Albany, Indiana, 2004-10-01
      - Mabel Scrivner interviewed by Sandra Marquez in New Albany, Indiana, 2004-10-01
      - Ronald Toran interviewed by Sandra Marquez in New Albany, Indiana, 2004-10-01
      - Anthony Toran interviewed by Sandra Marquez in New Albany, Indiana, 2004-10-01
      - W. Michael Roberts interviewed by Sandra Marquez in New Albany, Indiana, 2004-10-01
    - AFC 2005/015: SR241, 1 minidisc
      - George Neal interviewed by Sandra Marquez in Indianapolis, Indiana, 2004-10-02
      - A. R. Sales interviewed by Sandra Marquez in Indianapolis, Indiana, 2004-10-02
    - AFC 2005/015: SR242, 1 minidisc
      - George Van Sickles interviewed by Sandra Marquez in Indianapolis, Indiana, 2004-10-02
      - Juanita Easley interviewed by Sandra Marquez in Indianapolis, Indiana, 2004-10-02
    - AFC 2005/015: SR243, 1 minidisc
      - Madilene Ramsey interviewed by Sandra Marquez in Indianapolis, Indiana, 2004-10-02
    - AFC 2005/015: SR244, 1 minidisc
      - Betty Rutherford interviewed by Joe Nick Patoski in Detroit, Michigan, 2004-09-30
      - Hazel Whitney interviewed by Joe Nick Patoski in Detroit, Michigan, 2004-09-30
      - Ernest Allen, Sr., interviewed by Joe Nick Patoski in Detroit, Michigan, 2004-09-30
    - AFC 2005/015: SR245, 1 minidisc
      - Larry Mack interviewed by Joe Nick Patoski in Topeka, Kansas, 2004-10-08
      - Michael Yellow Bird interviewed by Joe Nick Patoski in Topeka, Kansas, 2004-10-08
      - Margaret Bradshaw interviewed by Joe Nick Patoski in Topeka, Kansas, 2004-10-08
    - AFC 2005/015: SR246, 1 minidisc
      - Sister Antona Ebo interviewed by Joe Nick Patoski in St. Louis, Missouri, 2004-10-06
      - Thelma Cahill interviewed by Joe Nick Patoski in St. Louis, Missouri, 2004-10-06
      - Robert Watson-Bey interviewed by Joe Nick Patoski in St. Louis, Missouri, 2004-10-06
      - Sam Fox interviewed by Joe Nick Patoski in St. Louis, Missouri, 2004-10-06
      - Jessie Mae Brown interviewed by Joe Nick Patoski in St. Louis, Missouri, 2004-10-06
    - AFC 2005/015: SR247, 1 minidisc
      - Sarah Ragin-Williams interviewed by Vern Smith in Columbia, South Carolina, 2004-08-09
    - AFC 2005/015: SR248, 1 minidisc
      - Mary Frances Mays interviewed by Vern Smith in Hayneville, Alabama, 2004-08-16
    - AFC 2005/015: SR249, 1 minidisc
      - Enola Mixon interviewed by Vern Smith in Las Vegas, Nevada, 2004-10-14
      - Grace Orange interviewed by Vern Smith in Las Vegas, Nevada, 2004-10-14
      - Betty Faoye interviewed by Vern Smith in Las Vegas, Nevada, 2004-10-14
      - Myraetta Speight interviewed by Vern Smith in Las Vegas, Nevada, 2004-10-14
    - AFC 2005/015: SR250, 1 minidisc
      - Norman Jackson interviewed by Vern Smith in Tallahassee, Florida, 2004-08-12
      - Josephine Newton interviewed by Vern Smith in Tallahassee, Florida, 2004-08-12
      - Deloris Darby interviewed by Vern Smith in Tallahassee, Florida, 2004-08-12
      - Eddie Randolph interviewed by Vern Smith in Tallahassee, Florida, 2004-08-12
    - AFC 2005/015: SR251, 1 minidisc
      - William Hernandez interviewed by Vern Smith in Las Vegas, Nevada, 2004-10
    - AFC 2005/015: SR252, 1 minidisc
      - Ned Cary interviewed by Vern Smith in Richmond, Virginia, 2004-08-04
      - Arthur St. John interviewed by Vern Smith in Richmond, Virginia, 2004-08-04
      - Anna Washington interviewed by Vern Smith in Richmond, Virginia, 2004-08-04
      - Salimah Hassan interviewed by Vern Smith in Richmond, Virginia, 2004-08-04
    - AFC 2005/015: SR253, 1 minidisc
      - Dwight Canady interviewed by Vern Smith in Topeka, Kansas, 2004-10-08
      - William Minner interviewed by Vern Smith in Topeka, Kansas, 2004-10-08
    - AFC 2005/015: SR254, 1 minidisc
      - Elizabeth Brown interviewed by Marilyn Mapp in Chicago, Illinois, 2004-10-04
      - Bobbi Ball interviewed by Marilyn Mapp in Chicago, Illinois, 2004-10-04
      - George O'Hare interviewed by Marilyn Mapp in Chicago, Illinois, 2004-10-04
    - AFC 2005/015: SR255, 1 minidisc
      - James Rucker interviewed by Joe Nick Patoski in Chicago, Illinois, 2004-10-04
    - AFC 2005/015: SR256, 1 minidisc
      - Ellis Raickett interviewed by Joe Nick Patoski in Chicago, Illinois, 2004-10-05
      - Bobby Davis interviewed by Joe Nick Patoski in Chicago, Illinois, 2004-10-05
      - Barbara Fulgear interviewed by Joe Nick Patoski in Chicago, Illinois, 2004-10-05
      - Dick Kelly interviewed by Joe Nick Patoski in Chicago, Illinois, 2004-10-05
      - Juanita Passmore interviewed by Joe Nick Patoski in Chicago, Illinois, 2004-10-05
      - Chestine Allen interviewed by Joe Nick Patoski in Chicago, Illinois, 2004-10-05
    - AFC 2005/015: SR257, 1 minidisc
      - Barbara Lawrence interviewed by Joe Nick Patoski in Chicago, Illinois, 2004-10-05
      - Helen Plicque interviewed by Joe Nick Patoski in Chicago, Illinois, 2004-10-05
      - Thelma Luther interviewed by Joe Nick Patoski in Chicago, Illinois, 2004-10-05
    - AFC 2005/015: SR258, 1 minidisc
      - Kathleen Pitts interviewed by Joe Nick Patoski in Milwaukee, Wisconsin, 2004-10-03
      - Thelma Bridgeford interviewed by Joe Nick Patoski in Milwaukee, Wisconsin, 2004-10-03
      - Warren Espinosa interviewed by Joe Nick Patoski in Chicago, Illinois, 2004-10-04
      - Jeremiah Jenkins, Jr., interviewed by Joe Nick Patoski in Chicago, Illinois, 2004-10-04
    - AFC 2005/015: SR259, 1 minidisc
      - Lucinda Gordon interviewed by Joe Nick Patoski in Milwaukee, Wisconsin, 2004-10-03 (1 of 2)
    - AFC 2005/015: SR260, 1 minidisc
      - Lucinda Gordon interviewed by Joe Nick Patoski in Milwaukee, Wisconsin, 2004-10-03 (2 of 2)
      - Llewellyn Eastern interviewed by Joe Nick Patoski in Milwaukee, Wisconsin, 2004-10-03
      - Robert Mays interviewed by Joe Nick Patoski in Milwaukee, Wisconsin, 2004-10-03
      - Ruth Zubrensky interviewed by Joe Nick Patoski in Milwaukee, Wisconsin, 2004-10-03
      - Evelyn Sims interviewed by Joe Nick Patoski in Milwaukee, Wisconsin, 2004-10-03
    - AFC 2005/015: SR261, 1 minidisc
      - Deborah Wesley interviewed by Joe Nick Patoski in New Albany, Indiana, 2004-10-01
      - Jerrol Miles interviewed by Joe Nick Patoski in New Albany, Indiana, 2004-10-01
      - Alice Miles interviewed by Joe Nick Patoski in New Albany, Indiana, 2004-10-01
      - Patricia Kinchlow interviewed by Joe Nick Patoski in New Albany, Indiana, 2004-10-01
      - David Kinchlow interviewed by Joe Nick Patoski in New Albany, Indiana, 2004-10-01
    - AFC 2005/015: SR262, 1 minidisc
      - Clifford Willis interviewed by Joe Nick Patoski in Indianapolis, Indiana, 2004-10-02
    - AFC 2005/015: SR263, 1 minidisc
      - Paula Harrison interviewed by Joe Nick Patoski in Indianapolis, Indiana, 2004-10-02
      - Brenda Rice interviewed by Joe Nick Patoski in Indianapolis, Indiana, 2004-10-02
      - Leroy Holmes, Jr., interviewed by Joe Nick Patoski in Indianapolis, Indiana, 2004-10-02
    - AFC 2005/015: SR264, 1 minidisc
      - Kay Kitayama interviewed by Joe Nick Patoski in Little Rock, Arkansas, 2004-09-25
      - Don Seki interviewed by Joe Nick Patoski in Little Rock, Arkansas, 2004-09-25
      - Midori Tani interviewed by Joe Nick Patoski in Little Rock, Arkansas, 2004-09-25
      - Bill Shishima interviewed by Joe Nick Patoski in Little Rock, Arkansas, 2004-09-25
    - AFC 2005/015: SR265, 1 minidisc
      - Jackie Johnson interviewed by Vern Smith in Washington, D.C., 2004-08-02
    - AFC 2005/015: SR266, 1 minidisc
      - Carmen Carrillo interviewed by Vern Smith in Las Vegas, Nevada, 2004-10-15
      - Deborah Montgomery interviewed by Vern Smith in Las Vegas, Nevada, 2004-10-15
      - Barbara Moore interviewed by Vern Smith in Las Vegas, Nevada, 2004-10-15
      - Christine Hely interviewed by Vern Smith in Las Vegas, Nevada, 2004-10-15
      - Willie Mae Barnes interviewed by Vern Smith in Las Vegas, Nevada, 2004-10-15
    - AFC 2005/015: SR267, 1 minidisc
      - George Harden interviewed by Vern Smith in Natchez, Mississippi, 2004-08-22
      - Semo Warren interviewed by Vern Smith in Natchez, Mississippi, 2004-08-22
      - Mamie Mazique interviewed by Vern Smith in Natchez, Mississippi, 2004-08-22
    - AFC 2005/015: SR268, 1 minidisc
      - David Fouche interviewed by Vern Smith in Jackson, Mississippi, 2004-08-19
      - Ineva May-Pittman interviewed by Vern Smith in Jackson, Mississippi, 2004-08-19
      - Helen Jackson interviewed by Vern Smith in Jackson, Mississippi, 2004-08-19
      - Gwendolyn Loper interviewed by Vern Smith in Jackson, Mississippi, 2004-08-19
    - AFC 2005/015: SR269, 1 minidisc
      - Dorothy Thomas interviewed by Vern Smith in Chicago, Illinois, 2004-10-06
      - Grace Vairin interviewed by Vern Smith in Chicago, Illinois, 2004-10-06
      - Theresa Joiner interviewed by Vern Smith in Chicago, Illinois, 2004-10-06
      - Anna Herron interviewed by Vern Smith in Chicago, Illinois, 2004-10-06
    - AFC 2005/015: SR270, 1 minidisc
      - Gay Kernan interviewed by Debra Krol in Hobbs, New Mexico, 2004-08-29
      - Betty Barnes interviewed by Debra Krol in Hobbs, New Mexico, 2004-08-29
      - Deborah Sarabia interviewed by Debra Krol in Hobbs, New Mexico, 2004-08-29
    - AFC 2005/015: SR271, 1 minidisc
      - John Feagin interviewed by Esther Iverem in Montgomery, Alabama, 2004-08-15
      - Frances Morgan interviewed by Esther Iverem in Montgomery, Alabama, 2004-08-15
      - Dorothea Huggins interviewed by Esther Iverem in Montgomery, Alabama, 2004-08-15
      - Lawrence Huggins interviewed by Esther Iverem in Montgomery, Alabama, 2004-08-15
      - Naomi Randolph interviewed by Esther Iverem in Montgomery, Alabama, 2004-08-15
    - AFC 2005/015: SR272, 1 minidisc
      - Carolyn Allen interviewed by Lydia Lum in New Orleans, Louisiana, 2004-08-24
      - Maurice Bush interviewed by Lydia Lum in New Orleans, Louisiana, 2004-08-24
      - Evelyn Adolphe interviewed by Lydia Lum in New Orleans, Louisiana, 2004-08-24
      - Rickey Reeves interviewed by Lydia Lum in New Orleans, Louisiana, 2004-08-24
      - Ernestine Keith interviewed by Lydia Lum in New Orleans, Louisiana, 2004-08-24
    - AFC 2005/015: SR273, 1 minidisc
      - Larshea Thomas interviewed by Sandra Marquez in Memphis, Tennessee, 2004-09-18
      - Mary Stockley interviewed by Sandra Marquez in Memphis, Tennessee, 2004-09-18
      - Clifford Browner interviewed by Sandra Marquez in Albany, Georgia, 2004-09-20
      - Michael Miller interviewed by Sandra Marquez in Albany, Georgia, 2004-09-20
    - AFC 2005/015: SR274, 1 minidisc
      - Lillian James interviewed by Sandra Marquez in Chicago, Illinois, 2004-10-05
      - Lucius Swilley interviewed by Sandra Marquez in Chicago, Illinois, 2004-10-05
      - Jessie Halbert interviewed by Sandra Marquez in Chicago, Illinois, 2004-10-05
      - Mary Lou Tardy interviewed by Sandra Marquez in Chicago, Illinois, 2004-10-05
      - Barbara Cordell interviewed by Sandra Marquez in Chicago, Illinois, 2004-10-05
      - Josie Nyireda-DeCosta interviewed by Sandra Marquez in Chicago, Illinois, 2004-10-05 (1 of 2)
    - AFC 2005/015: SR275, 1 minidisc
      - Josie Nyireda-DeCosta interviewed by Sandra Marquez in Chicago, Illinois, 2004-10-05 (2 of 2)
      - Mae Travis interviewed by Sandra Marquez in St. Louis, Missouri, 2004-10-06
      - Lakshmi Hingorani interviewed by Sandra Marquez in St. Louis, Missouri, 2004-10-06
      - Sheldon Katz interviewed by Sandra Marquez in St. Louis, Missouri, 2004-10-06
      - Lois Perryman interviewed by Sandra Marquez in St. Louis, Missouri, 2004-10-06
    - AFC 2005/015: SR276, 1 minidisc
      - Inez Willie interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Chicago, Illinois, 2004-10-05
      - Audley Mackel, Jr., interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Chicago, Illinois, 2004-10-05
      - Thomas Ramsey interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Chicago, Illinois, 2004-10-05
      - Geraldine Flowers interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Chicago, Illinois, 2004-10-05
      - Joyce McGuire-Teasley interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Chicago, Illinois, 2004-10-05 (2 of 2)
    - AFC 2005/015: SR277, 1 minidisc
      - Raymond Frazier interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Little Rock, Arkansas, 2004-09-25
      - Orealious Moore interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Little Rock, Arkansas, 2004-09-25
      - Thelma Wair interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Little Rock, Arkansas, 2004-09-25
      - Lorene Watson Joshua interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Little Rock, Arkansas, 2004-09-25
      - Kathleen Woods interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Little Rock, Arkansas, 2004-09-25
      - Mabel Harris interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Little Rock, Arkansas, 2004-09-25
      - Carolyn Hobbs interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Little Rock, Arkansas, 2004-09-25
      - Linnie Hood interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Little Rock, Arkansas, 2004-09-25
      - Christine Gatewood interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Little Rock, Arkansas, 2004-09-25
      - Verma Simmons interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Little Rock, Arkansas, 2004-09-25
      - Bob Uyeyama interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Little Rock, Arkansas, 2004-09-25
      - Gary Shiota interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Little Rock, Arkansas, 2004-09-25 (1 of 2)
    - AFC 2005/015: SR278, 1 minidisc
      - Joe Snead interviewed by Vern Smith in Albany, Georgia, 2004-09-20
      - Rachel Young-Allen interviewed by Vern Smith in Albany, Georgia, 2004-09-20
      - Willie Adams interviewed by Vern Smith in Albany, Georgia, 2004-09-20
      - Henry Mathis, Jr., interviewed by Vern Smith in Albany, Georgia, 2004-09-20
      - Etris Smith, Sr., interviewed by Vern Smith in Albany, Georgia, 2004-09-20
      - Rutha Mae Harris interviewed by Vern Smith in Albany, Georgia, 2004-09-20
    - AFC 2005/015: SR279, 1 minidisc
      - Lucretia Green interviewed by Vern Smith in Summerton, South Carolina, 2004-08-08
      - Octavia Briggs interviewed by Vern Smith in Summerton, South Carolina, 2004-08-08
      - Carrie Sinkler-Parker interviewed by Vern Smith in Summerton, South Carolina, 2004-08-08
      - Nathaniel Briggs interviewed by Vern Smith in Summerton, South Carolina, 2004-08-08
      - Darrollyn Taylor interviewed by Vern Smith in Columbia, South Carolina, 2004-08-08
      - Violet Staley interviewed by Vern Smith in Columbia, South Carolina, 2004-08-08
      - Pamela Burgess interviewed by Vern Smith in Columbia, South Carolina, 2004-08-08
      - Claudette Pauling interviewed by Vern Smith in Orangeburg, South Carolina, 2004-08-09
    - AFC 2005/015: SR280, 1 minidisc
      - David Moore interviewed by Vern Smith in Greensboro, North Carolina, 2004-08-05
      - Hubert Westmoreland interviewed by Vern Smith in Greensboro, North Carolina, 2004-08-05
      - Ronnie Quick interviewed by Vern Smith in Greensboro, North Carolina, 2004-08-05
      - Donald Matthews interviewed by Vern Smith in Greensboro, North Carolina, 2004-08-05
    - AFC 2005/015: SR281, 1 minidisc
      - Zylpha Garrett interviewed by Vern Smith in Columbus, Ohio, 2004-09-28
      - Donnel Thomas interviewed by Vern Smith in Columbus, Ohio, 2004-09-28
    - AFC 2005/015: SR282, 1 minidisc
      - Yolanda Mitchell interviewed by Vern Smith in Durham, North Carolina, 2004-08-05
      - Floyd McKissick, Jr., interviewed by Vern Smith in Durham, North Carolina, 2004-08-05
      - Warren Herndon interviewed by Vern Smith in Durham, North Carolina, 2004-08-05
      - Geneva Watts interviewed by Vern Smith in Durham, North Carolina, 2004-08-05
      - Doxie Whitfield interviewed by Vern Smith in Durham, North Carolina, 2004-08-05
      - Pat Levitin interviewed by Vern Smith in Greensboro, North Carolina, 2004-08-06
      - Tricia Hairsten interviewed by Vern Smith in Greensboro, North Carolina, 2004-08-06
      - Corene Blair interviewed by Vern Smith in Greensboro, North Carolina, 2004-08-06
      - Patricia Fortune interviewed by Vern Smith in Greensboro, North Carolina, 2004-08-06
    - AFC 2005/015: SR283, 1 minidisc
      - Gwendolyn Gamble interviewed by Vern Smith in Birmingham, Alabama, 2004-08-14
      - Deborah Avery interviewed by Vern Smith in Birmingham, Alabama, 2004-08-14
      - Catherine Burks-Brooks interviewed by Vern Smith in Birmingham, Alabama, 2004-08-14
    - AFC 2005/015: SR284, 1 minidisc
      - Kirk Jones interviewed by Vern Smith in Richmond, Virginia, 2004-08-04
      - Pauline Latta interviewed by Vern Smith in Raleigh, North Carolina, 2004-08-05
      - Doris Burke interviewed by Vern Smith in Raleigh, North Carolina, 2004-08-05
      - Mary Poole interviewed by Vern Smith in Raleigh, North Carolina, 2004-08-05
      - Marsha Harris interviewed by Vern Smith in Raleigh, North Carolina, 2004-08-05
    - AFC 2005/015: SR285, 1 minidisc
      - Gwen Britt interviewed by Vern Smith in Washington, D.C.
    - AFC 2005/015: SR286, 1 minidisc
      - Frederick James interviewed by Vern Smith in Columbia, South Carolina, 2004-08-09
    - AFC 2005/015: SR287, 1 minidisc
      - Nathaniel Hill interviewed by Vern Smith in Little Rock, Arkansas, 2004-09
      - Vernita Humphrey interviewed by Vern Smith in Little Rock, Arkansas, 2004-09
    - AFC 2005/015: SR288, 1 minidisc
      - E. Elaine Geeter interviewed by Vern Smith in Montgomery, Alabama, 2004-08-15
      - James Jackson interviewed by Vern Smith in Selma, Alabama, 2004-08-16
      - Ethel Jemison interviewed by Vern Smith in Selma, Alabama, 2004-08-16
    - AFC 2005/015: SR289, 1 minidisc
      - Burrell Pollard interviewed by Vern Smith in Richmond, Virginia, 2004-08-03
      - Oliver Hill interviewed by Vern Smith in Richmond, Virginia, 2004-08-03
    - AFC 2005/015: SR290, 1 minidisc
      - Richard Henry interviewed by Vern Smith in Albany, Georgia, 2004-09-20
      - Elza Pat Horton interviewed by Vern Smith in Albany, Georgia, 2004-09-20
      - Emory Harris interviewed by Vern Smith in Albany, Georgia, 2004-09-20
    - AFC 2005/015: SR291, 1 minidisc
      - Hertha Taylor interviewed by Vern Smith in Indianapolis, Indiana, 2004-10-02
      - Jacqui Tanner interviewed by Vern Smith in Indianapolis, Indiana, 2004-10-02
      - Leola Hunt-Rush interviewed by Vern Smith in Indianapolis, Indiana, 2004-10-02
    - AFC 2005/015: SR292, 1 minidisc
      - Lucille Berrien interviewed by Vern Smith in Milwaukee, Wisconsin, 2004-10-03
      - George Nevels interviewed by Vern Smith in Milwaukee, Wisconsin, 2004-10-03
      - Ifama Jackson interviewed by Vern Smith in Milwaukee, Wisconsin, 2004-10-03 (1 of 2)
    - AFC 2005/015: SR293, 1 minidisc
      - Ifama Jackson interviewed by Vern Smith in Milwaukee, Wisconsin, 2004-10-03 (2 of 2)
      - Joe Crawford interviewed by Vern Smith in Milwaukee, Wisconsin, 2004-10-03
      - Harry Kemp interviewed by Vern Smith in Milwaukee, Wisconsin, 2004-10-03
    - AFC 2005/015: SR294, 1 minidisc
      - Orlando Rambo interviewed by Vern Smith in Albany, Georgia, 2004-09-20
    - AFC 2005/015: SR295, 1 minidisc
      - Marlene Johnson-Odom interviewed by Marilyn Mapp in Milwaukee, Wisconsin, 2004-10-04
      - Eddie Martin, Jr., interviewed by Marilyn Mapp in Milwaukee, Wisconsin, 2004-10-04
      - Louise Wilhite interviewed by Marilyn Mapp in Milwaukee, Wisconsin, 2004-10-04
      - Eugene Bleidorn interviewed by Marilyn Mapp in Milwaukee, Wisconsin, 2004-10-04
      - Mary Agnes Blonien interviewed by Marilyn Mapp in Milwaukee, Wisconsin, 2004-10-04
    - AFC 2005/015: SR296, 1 minidisc
      - Barbara Crehmer interviewed by Joe Nick Patoski in Macon, Georgia, 2004-09-21
      - Odessa Howard interviewed by Joe Nick Patoski in Macon, Georgia, 2004-09-21
      - Myrna Bell interviewed by Joe Nick Patoski in Macon, Georgia, 2004-09-21
      - Marie Jones interviewed by Joe Nick Patoski in Macon, Georgia, 2004-09-21
    - AFC 2005/015: SR297, 1 minidisc
      - Mildred Finney interviewed by Joe Nick Patoski in Macon, Georgia, 2004-09-21
      - Rosa McKendric interviewed by Joe Nick Patoski in Macon, Georgia, 2004-09-21
      - Betty Samson interviewed by Joe Nick Patoski in Macon, Georgia, 2004-09-21
      - Jimmy Mills, Jr., interviewed by Joe Nick Patoski in Macon, Georgia, 2004-09-21
    - AFC 2005/015: SR298, 1 minidisc